Peace and Justice Studies Records UA086
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Curricula, 1980 -- 2010; UA086.002; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - Advising/ Component Dev., 1987; UA086.002.009.00013 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - Course Readings, 1980; UA086.002.009.00014 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - Grinnell College Study, 1998; UA086.002.009.00015 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - Service Learning, 1995 -- 1999; UA086.002.009.00016 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - Citizen & Public Service Advising, 2001; UA086.002.009.00017 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - CSL Literature, 2000; UA086.002.009.00018 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - Course Literature/ Materials, 2000; UA086.002.009.00019 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - PJS001, 1990 -- 2001; UA086.002.009.00020 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - Intro to PJS, 1989; UA086.002.009.00021 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - PJS '93 Intro, 1993; UA086.002.009.00022 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - PJS Intro, Spring, 1993; UA086.002.009.00023 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - Intro Prep, Folder 1 of 2, 1994; UA086.002.009.00024 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - Intro Prep, Folder 2 of 2, 1994; UA086.002.009.00025 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - PJS01, Spring, 1995; UA086.002.009.00026 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - PJS Intro, Spring, 1995; UA086.002.009.00027 (Box UA086 Shared 1)
  - PJS001 - Intro, Haley Duschinski, 2003; UA086.002.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - PJS120 Evaluations, 1999; UA086.002.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - PJS135, Fall, 2002; UA086.002.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - PJS190, Neta Crawford, Spring, 1993; UA086.002.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - PJS190 Evaluation, Spring, 2003; UA086.002.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Affinity Groups, 1999; UA086.002.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Affinity Group Projects, 1994; UA086.002.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Intro Affinity Group Sites, 1997; UA086.002.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Affinity Group Project, 2000; UA086.002.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Affinity Group, 2001; UA086.002.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Massachusetts Coalition for the Homeless, 2001; UA086.002.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - American Anti-Slavery Group, 2001; UA086.002.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 2001; UA086.002.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Infact, 2001; UA086.002.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Eagle Eye Group, 2001; UA086.002.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Affinity Groups, 2003; UA086.002.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Affinity Group, 2004; UA086.002.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Affinity Group, Fall, 2005; UA086.002.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - EXP 41 P7, Fall, 1985; UA086.002.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - Toward A Just World Order, Freida Gerry, 1987; UA086.002.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - Rap As Revolution, 1992; UA086.002.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - Exploration, 1994; UA086.002.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - EX-17, Fall, 1999; UA086.002.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - Social Activism Exploration, Ginny & Brian, 1991; UA086.002.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - Exploration, Recent Protest Literature, 1995; UA086.002.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - Women's Studies- Intro, 1998; UA086.002.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - Narrative and American Identity, 1998; UA086.002.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Syllabi, 2001 -- 2004; UA086.002.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - Course Listings, 2002 -- 2003; UA086.002.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Classes, Fall, 1999; UA086.002.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - Classes, Spring, 2004; UA086.002.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Sarah Conn, 1989; UA086.002.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - Advanced Seminar, Paul Walker, Disinventing the Bomb, 1988; UA086.002.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - Spring Internship Revision, 2002; UA086.002.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Internship Task Force, 1992; UA086.002.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Internship Brochure, 2001; UA086.002.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Internship Mailing List- Update/Letter, 1997; UA086.002.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Internships, 1987 -- 1988; UA086.002.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Internship Research, 1991 -- 1992; UA086.002.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Leadership Meeting Group, 1986; UA086.002.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Service Learning Professional Development, 2000; UA086.002.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Service/ Experiential Education Literature, 1997 -- 1998; UA086.002.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - At Conf: Is Everybody Learning?, 2004; UA086.002.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Citizenship Literature, 2003; UA086.002.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Campus Compact, 1995; UA086.002.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Best Practices in Cyber-Serve, 1999; UA086.002.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Service Learning Lit, 1994 -- 1999; UA086.002.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - 1995 Teli Workshop, UA086.002.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Researching Climate Change, 2008; UA086.002.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - MCAN Advisory Group, 2009; UA086.002.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - TPEC Related, 1995 -- 1996; UA086.002.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - EE Project/Proposal, 1989; UA086.002.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - S-L Discussion Group, 1994 -- 1996; UA086.002.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - PSTF Summer Institute, 1997; UA086.002.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - UCCPS, 1999 -- 2001; UA086.002.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - MWC, 2000; UA086.002.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - UCCPS Watershed Institute, 2001; UA086.002.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - UCCPS Report/Meeting on Community P-Ships, 2001; UA086.002.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Media & Public Service, 2004 -- 2006; UA086.002.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - International Internships & Study Abroad, 2006; UA086.002.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - Underground Railroad Residency, 2006; UA086.002.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Tisch College Adjunct, 2010; UA086.002.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - Various Tisch Professional Development, 1999; UA086.002.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - OISE, 2003; UA086.002.011.00031 (Box 11)
- Professional Development, 1987 -- 2006; UA086.003; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains records of internal and external professional development opportunities from 1987 to 2006. Materials include conference notes, planning documents, and career fair information. Files deal with the New England Peace Studies Association and Educators for Peace.
  This series is arranged by date.
  - Interfaith Peace Network, Spring 1987 Conference, UA086.003.012.00001 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - National Peace Studies Association, 1987 Formation, UA086.003.012.00002 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Regional Consortium, NEPSA, 1987 -- 1988; UA086.003.012.00003 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Peace Studies Assoc. Annual Meeting, 1988 -- 1989; UA086.003.012.00004 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Peace Studies Assoc., 1988 -- 1991; UA086.003.012.00005 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - On Violence and Human Rights, Summer Institute, 1989; UA086.003.012.00006 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Common Security Institute, 1989; UA086.003.012.00007 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Peace Studies Association, 1990 -- 1991; UA086.003.012.00008 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - NEPSA [New England Peace Studies Association], 1991 -- 1992; UA086.003.012.00009 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Peace Studies Association, Folder 1 of 2, 1992 -- 1993; UA086.003.012.00010 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Peace Studies Association, Folder 2 of 2, 1992 -- 1993; UA086.003.012.00011 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Public Service Task Force, 1993 -- 1996; UA086.003.012.00012 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - PEACE Discussion Group, 1994 -- 1997; UA086.003.012.00013 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Planning Documents (PSA), 1994; UA086.003.012.00014 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - PSA [Peace Studies Association] Annual Meeting, 1995; UA086.003.012.00015 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - New England Organizing Conference for Nuclear Weapons Abolition, 1997; UA086.003.012.00016 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - PSA/COPRED Conference, 1997; UA086.003.012.00017 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - PSA/COPRED, 1998; UA086.003.012.00018 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Educators for Peace Working Group, 1998 -- 1999; UA086.003.012.00019 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Hague Appeal, 1999; UA086.003.012.00020 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Global Campaign for Peace Ed., 1999; UA086.003.012.00021 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - BRC-NEPSA Planning, 1999; UA086.003.012.00022 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Children in IR [International Relations], 2002; UA086.003.012.00023 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - AFSC/Reflection Group, 1995; UA086.003.012.00024 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Americorps Visits, 2004; UA086.003.012.00025 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - Practicing Democracy Project- M. Ganz, 2005 -- 2006; UA086.003.012.00026 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - COPRED, 1988 -- 1993; UA086.003.012.00027 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
- Co-curricular, 1987 -- 2010; UA086.004; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains materials related to service learning and voluntarism, as well as other co-curricular projects taking place between 1987 and 2010. Materials include conference notes, service learning literature, and files relating to the Leonard Carmichael Association.
  This series is arranged by topic and date.
  - PJS Awards Party, 2004 -- 2010; UA086.004.012.00028 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - ORG./Career Fair Ideas, 1996; UA086.004.012.00029 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - "Decade" Advising Planning, 2000 -- 2010; UA086.004.012.00030 (Box UA086 Shared 2)
  - [Campus Compact], 1995; UA086.004.013.00001 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - [Civil Society Development Program], 1994; UA086.004.013.00002 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Alverno College Conference, 1993; UA086.004.013.00003 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Course and Program Assessment for the Experiential Educator, 1994; UA086.004.013.00004 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Service Learning Literature, 2004; UA086.004.013.00005 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Leonard Carmichael Society, 1987 -- 1993; UA086.004.013.00006 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Tufts Custodians, 1997; UA086.004.013.00007 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Anti-War (Iraq) Organizing, 1998; UA086.004.013.00008 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Allies Group, 1996; UA086.004.013.00009 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
- Internal Administration, 1983 -- 2006; UA086.005; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series consists of Executive Board Minutes and Annual Reports taking place between 1983 and 2006. Materials also focus on program planning and development, program proposals, group organization and structure, open house meetings, reports, announcements, fellowships, degree requirements, course evaluations, and fundraising. This series contains files relating to the Center for Interdisciplinary Studies.
  This series is arranged into two sub-series, arranged by date.
  - Program Planning, 1984 -- 1985; UA086.005.013.00010 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Annual Report, 1984 -- 1985; UA086.005.013.00011 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - PJS Program Proposal, 1985; UA086.005.013.00012 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Development of Program, 1985; UA086.005.013.00013 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - PJS Flyer: Orientation Handout, 1985; UA086.005.013.00014 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - New Brochure Layout, 1985; UA086.005.013.00015 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Alumni/Donor Development, 1985 -- 1986; UA086.005.013.00016 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - PJS Organization/Structure, 1985 -- 1986; UA086.005.013.00017 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Open House Meeting, 1986 -- 1987; UA086.005.013.00018 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - End Year Reports, 1989 -- 1994; UA086.005.013.00019 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Newsletter: Notes/Materials, 1987; UA086.005.013.00020 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - PJS External Review, 1989; UA086.005.013.00021 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - External Review, 1989; UA086.005.013.00022 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - PJS 5 Year Report, 2003; UA086.005.013.00023 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - PJS Planning, 2000; UA086.005.013.00024 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Graduation Pledge, 2005 -- 2006; UA086.005.013.00025 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Peace and Social Justice, 1983 -- 1984; UA086.005.013.00026 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Degree Requirements, 2000; UA086.005.013.00027 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - List Updates, 2000; UA086.005.013.00028 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - PJS "How to Do" Info Sheets, 2000; UA086.005.013.00029 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - PJS Miscellaneous, 1990 -- 2001; UA086.005.013.00030 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Announcements/Fellowships to Post, 1998 -- 1999; UA086.005.013.00031 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - PJS Advertisements, 1998 -- 2002; UA086.005.013.00032 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Flyers, 2002; UA086.005.013.00033 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - New Brochure, UA086.005.013.00034 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - First Year Advisors, 1986 -- 1993; UA086.005.013.00035 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Somekh Social Justice Fund, 2000; UA086.005.013.00036 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - New Student Folder, 1993 -- 1997; UA086.005.013.00037 (Box UA086 Shared 3)
  - Peace and Justice Executive Board, Student Information, 1997 -- 1998; UA086.005.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - XBD, 1996 -- 1999; UA086.005.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - XBD [Executive Board], 1999 -- 2000; UA086.005.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Interdisciplinary Center Formation, Folder 1 of 2, 1992 -- 1993; UA086.005.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Interdisciplinary Center Formation, Folder 2 of 2, 1992 -- 1993; UA086.005.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - CIS [Center for Interdisciplinary Studies], 1994 -- 1995; UA086.005.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - CIS, 1997 -- 1998; UA086.005.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Conversations, 1997 -- 1998; UA086.005.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - CIS, 1998 -- 1999; UA086.005.014.00009 (Box 14)
  - LIS Board, 2000 -- 2001; UA086.005.014.00010 (Box 14)
  - CIS Board, 2001 -- 2002; UA086.005.014.00011 (Box 14)
  - LIS Meetings, 2002 -- 2003; UA086.005.014.00012 (Box 14)
  - Women's Health-Community Health Program, 2000; UA086.005.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - EJ Workshop Training, 2001; UA086.005.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - EJAM [Environmental Justice Across the Mystic], 2002; UA086.005.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Environmental Justice Training, 2003; UA086.005.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - MWC Steering Committee, 2003 -- 2004; UA086.005.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - EJAM Final Report, 2005; UA086.005.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - EJAM Chapter/Julian, 2003; UA086.005.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - EJAM Data Analysis, 2003 -- 2004; UA086.005.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - MWC Conference, Community Service, 2000; UA086.005.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - New Century Env. Lead. Inst. Evals, 2000; UA086.005.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - CIS Course Evals, 2003; UA086.005.014.00023 (Box 14)
  - AWSEAM Draft, 2003; UA086.005.014.00024 (Box 14)
  - AWSEAM Workshop, 2004; UA086.005.014.00025 (Box 14)
  - CIS99/100 Course Evals, 2005; UA086.005.014.00026 (Box 14)
  - CIS99/100 Env. Leader Intern., 2005; UA086.005.014.00027 (Box 14)
  - Michelle Loquine, 2005; UA086.005.014.00028 (Box 14)
  - Kara Kelly, 2005; UA086.005.014.00029 (Box 14)
  - Alana Van der Mude, 2005; UA086.005.014.00030 (Box 14)
  - Hillary Shayne Research Project, 2006; UA086.005.014.00031 (Box 14)
  - Ben Rubinstein, 2005; UA086.005.014.00032 (Box 14)
  - Proposal Ideas for Grant Projects, 2004; UA086.005.014.00033 (Box 14)
  - PJSP Annual Report, 1989 -- 1990; UA086.005.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - PJSP Annual Report, 1990 -- 1991; UA086.005.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - PJSP Annual Report, 1991 -- 1992; UA086.005.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - PJSP Annual Report, 1996 -- 1997; UA086.005.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Internships, 1987 -- 1989; UA086.005.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - EXP40 PS Social Movements, 1985 -- 1988; UA086.005.014.00039 (Box 14)
  - Intern Clearinghouse Proposal, 1986 -- 1988; UA086.005.014.00040 (Box 14)
  - Fundraising, 1985; UA086.005.014.00041 (Box 14)
  - Funding Proposals, 1988; UA086.005.014.00042 (Box 14)
  - Programming, 1983 -- 1985; UA086.005.014.00043 (Box 14)
- Event Files, 1984 -- 1999; UA086.006; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series consists of event files from 1984 through 1999. Materials focus on speakers, film series, educational series, community relations notes, photo exhibits, education panels, and workshops.
  - Forum/West Germany Speakers, 1984; UA086.006.015.00001 (Box 15)
    Event Files
  - Kent Norsworthy Event, 1984; UA086.006.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Time of Daring, 1984; UA086.006.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Course and Film Series Publicity, 1984; UA086.006.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Film Series, 1984; UA086.006.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Educational Series, 1985; UA086.006.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Militarization of Outer Space, 1986; UA086.006.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Nuclear War Fighting, 1986; UA086.006.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Nuclear Awareness Project, 1986; UA086.006.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - Medford Outreach, 1986; UA086.006.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Community Relations Notes, 1986; UA086.006.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Somerville Outreach, 1986; UA086.006.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Options Resource Packet, 1986; UA086.006.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Middle East Film Series, 1986; UA086.006.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Jim Harney Photo Exhibit, 1986; UA086.006.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Ghaza Ghetto, From the West Bank to Armageddon, 1986; UA086.006.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Educationals, 1985; UA086.006.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Sanctuary: The Spirit of Harriet Tubman, 1986; UA086.006.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Educational Series "Think Globally, Act Locally", 1986; UA086.006.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Educational Series, 1986 -- 1987; UA086.006.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Nuclear Education Weekend, Milton Academy, 1987; UA086.006.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Open Block Discussions, 1987; UA086.006.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Educational Series, 1986 -- 1987; UA086.006.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Pedagogy Discussions, 1987 -- 1988; UA086.006.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - Welcome Back Party, Ziggys, 1988; UA086.006.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - Historical Memory, 1988; UA086.006.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - Film Series "Before the Big Chill", 1988; UA086.006.015.00027 (Box 15)
  - Educationals, 1988; UA086.006.015.00028 (Box 15)
  - Justice "Dialogues", 1988; UA086.006.015.00029 (Box 15)
  - Educational Series, 1989; UA086.006.015.00030 (Box 15)
  - Changing Our Minds, 1989; UA086.006.015.00031 (Box 15)
  - Steve Hoffman Events, 1989; UA086.006.015.00032 (Box 15)
  - Bruce Payne Visit, 1989; UA086.006.015.00033 (Box 15)
  - Children of War, 1990; UA086.006.015.00034 (Box 15)
  - Iraq: Media "Nonviolence", 1990; UA086.006.015.00035 (Box 15)
  - Education Panel, 1990; UA086.006.015.00036 (Box 15)
  - Race Environment, 1990 -- 1991; UA086.006.015.00037 (Box 15)
  - Gulf Crisis, 1991; UA086.006.015.00038 (Box 15)
  - Mary Link Workshop, 1991; UA086.006.015.00039 (Box 15)
  - Lorene Wapotich Exhibit, 1991; UA086.006.015.00040 (Box 15)
  - LEAD Workshops, 1991; UA086.006.016.00001 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Conscientious Objector Event, 1991; UA086.006.016.00002 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - PB&J, 1991 -- 1992; UA086.006.016.00003 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Doug McAdam, 1992; UA086.006.016.00004 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Modes of Resistance, 1992; UA086.006.016.00005 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Race and Rebellion, 1992; UA086.006.016.00006 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Military Waste/Environment, 1992; UA086.006.016.00007 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - PB&J, 1992 -- 1993; UA086.006.016.00008 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Women and Militarism, 1993; UA086.006.016.00009 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - PB&J, 1993 -- 1994; UA086.006.016.00010 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Events, 1993 -- 1994; UA086.006.016.00011 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Greetings From Iraq, 1994; UA086.006.016.00012 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Haiti Invasion, 1994; UA086.006.016.00013 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - PCSD Second Nature, 1995; UA086.006.016.00014 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Harry Wu Lecture, 1995; UA086.006.016.00015 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - PB&J, 1995 -- 1997; UA086.006.016.00016 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Scapegoats and Stereotypes, 1996; UA086.006.016.00017 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Day Without Violence, 1996; UA086.006.016.00018 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - PJS Open House, 1996; UA086.006.016.00019 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Power, 1997; UA086.006.016.00020 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Abolition 2000, 1997; UA086.006.016.00021 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Year of Nonviolence, 1998; UA086.006.016.00022 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - PB&J, 1997 -- 1998; UA086.006.016.00023 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - ML King Birthday, A Year of Nonviolence, 1998; UA086.006.016.00024 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - NEPSA/BRC, 1998; UA086.006.016.00025 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Women's Rights Are Human Rights, 1998; UA086.006.016.00026 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Face to Face in Conflict, 1999; UA086.006.016.00027 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Vincent Harding, 1999; UA086.006.016.00028 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Events, 1999; UA086.006.016.00029 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Decade of Nonviolence, 1999; UA086.006.016.00030 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
- Student Work, 1988 -- 1994; UA086.007; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of student capstone projects and theses from 1988 to 1994.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by creator.
  - Multicultural Resources for Elementary Students, 1992; UA086.007.016.00031 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
    Capstone projects.
  - Protest Art, Artful Protest by Matt Offenbacher, 1993; UA086.007.016.00032 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Power and Movement Process by David R. Lagasse, 1990; UA086.007.016.00033 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Student Activism at Tufts by David R. Lagasse, 1988; UA086.007.016.00034 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Activism at Tufts by Lisa Tanzer, 1988; UA086.007.016.00035 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - A History of the Student South African Divestment Campaign, 1994; UA086.007.016.00036 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Separate and Unequal by Samantha Langbaum, 1989; UA086.007.016.00037 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
  - Life After Death, Docudrama by Matt Offenbacher, 1994; UA086.007.016.00038 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
    videocassette
- Publications and Publicity, 1984 -- 1998; UA086.008; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains brochures and other promotional materials related to the Peace and Justice Studies Program from 1984 to 1998. Materials include executive board meeting notes and daily worksheets.
  - Old Brochures, UA086.008.016.00039 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
    Publicity
  - Peace and Justice Newsletter, 1986; UA086.008.016.00040 (Box UA086 Shared 4)
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - Board, 1984 -- 1985; UA086.008.017.00001 (Box 17)
    X-Board Meetings
  - Board Minutes/Notes, 1985 -- 1986; UA086.008.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Board Meetings, 1986 -- 1987; UA086.008.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Board Meetings, 1988 -- 1989; UA086.008.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Board Notes, 1989 -- 1990; UA086.008.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - X Board Meetings, 1989 -- 1990; UA086.008.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Executive Board, 1989 -- 1990; UA086.008.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - X Board Meetings, 1990 -- 1991; UA086.008.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - X Board Meetings, 1991 -- 1992; UA086.008.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - X Board, 1992 -- 1993; UA086.008.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - X Board, 1993 -- 1994; UA086.008.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - X Board Meetings, 1994 -- 1995; UA086.008.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - X Board, 1995 -- 1996; UA086.008.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - X Board, 1996 -- 1997; UA086.008.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Board Notes, 1998; UA086.008.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1984 -- 1985; UA086.008.017.00016 (Box 17)
    Daily Worksheets
  - Daily Worksheets, 1985 -- 1986; UA086.008.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1986 -- 1987; UA086.008.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1987 -- 1988; UA086.008.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1988 -- 1989; UA086.008.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1989 -- 1990; UA086.008.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1990 -- 1991; UA086.008.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1991 -- 1992; UA086.008.017.00023 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1992 -- 1993; UA086.008.017.00024 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1993 -- 1994; UA086.008.017.00025 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1994 -- 1995; UA086.008.017.00026 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1995 -- 1996; UA086.008.017.00027 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1996 -- 1997; UA086.008.017.00028 (Box 17)
  - Daily Worksheets, 1997 -- 1998; UA086.008.017.00029 (Box 17)
- 2017 accessions, circa 1980 -- 2015; UA086.009; Bryan, Dale; 6 Linear Feet
  University records are closed for 20 years from the date of creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by Peace and Justice Studies director Erin Kelley, 2017, accession UA-2018-016.
  This series is arranged in received order.